A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject files of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1972-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 31515], 1970-1981, Extent: cu. ft. (boxes). (Box 1-)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Northern Virginia Training Center for the Mentally Retarded, 1978-1981 (Box 33)
  - General Assembly, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Commission on H.B. 1935, 1978-1981 (Box 33)
  - General Assembly, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Bagley Commission, 1978-1979 (Box 33)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, General, 1978-1981 (Box 34)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Personnel (Review for privacy), 1978-1981 (Box 34)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Personnel (Review for privacy), 1978-1981 (Box 35)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Substance Abuse, 1978-1981 (Box 35)
  - Governor, Virginia Substance Abuse Advisory Council, 1978-1981 (Box 35)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, General, 1978-1981 (Box 36)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Board, 1978-1981 (Box 36)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Highway Labor, 1978-1981 (Box 36)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Legislation, 1978-1981 (Box 36)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Personnel (Review for privacy), 1978-1981 (Box 36)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Placement of Children, 1978-1981 (Box 37)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Prescription Team, 1978-1981 (Box 37)
  - Plaque for Otis L. Brown, Demolition of unsafe building at Lynchburg Training School and Hospital, 1978-1981 (Box 37)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Substance Abuse, 1978-1981 (Box 37)
  - Analysis of Population, Health, and Environment Relations in Virginia (Robert H. Giles, Jr.), 1974 (Box 38)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Medicaid, Medical Assistance Program, 1978-1981 (Box 38)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, General, 1978-1981 (Box 38)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Division of Water Program, 1978-1981 (Box 39)
  - Governor, Advisory Committee on Radioactive Waste Management, 1978-1981 (Box 39)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Statewide Health Coordinating Council, 1978-1981 (Box 39)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Health Care in Mental Health and Mental Retardation Institutions and Corrections Facilities, 1978-1981 (Box 40)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Medicaid fraud, 1978-1981 (Box 40)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Medicaid Management Assessment Report (Draft), Prepared by HealthCare Financing Administration, 1978-1979 (Box 40)
  - U.S. Dept. of Health, Education, and Welfare, The Secretary's National Conference on Fraud, Abuse, and Error: Protecting the Taxpayer's Dollar, Conference Proceedings 1978 December 13-14 (Box 40)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Division of Solid and Hazardous Waste, 1978-1981 (Box 40)
  - State Programs Supporting Health Manpower Training: An Inventory, Volume II, 1978-1981 (Box 41)
  - Summary and Analysis of Public Comments on Draft 1980-1984 State Health Plan and Plan Development Committee Recommended Revisions to Draft Plan, 1980 July (Box 41)
  - Dept. for Health Center for Health Statistics, Statistical Annual Report, 1978 (Box 41)
  - Governor, Advisory Committee on Radioactive Waste Management, 1978-1981 (Box 41)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Medicaid, Medical Assistance Program, 1978-1981 (Box 41)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, General, 1978-1981 (Box 42)
  - Report on Health Care Needs of Ambulatory Elderly, 1978-1981 (Box 42)
  - Eastern Virginia Health Systems Agency, Inc., An Application for Renewal of Full Designation of a Health Systems Agency for Eastern Virginia, 1978-1981 (Box 42)
  - Dept. of Health, Education, and Welfare, Requirements for Minority Statistics Report on an Expert Panel Meeting Supported by the Office of Health Resources Opportunity and the National Center for Health Statistics, Final report, 1979 (Box 42)
  - Review of Options to Contain the Cost of the Virginia Medical Assistance Program, Final report, 1979 (Box 42)
  - Northwestern Virginia Health Systems Agency, Inc., Draft grant application, 1978-1979 (Box 42)
  - Northwestern Virginia Health Systems Agency, Inc., Annual Implementation Plan, 1978-1979 (Box 42)
  - Northwestern Virginia Health Systems Agency, Inc., Health Systems Plan for Virginia's Health Service Area I, 1978-1979 (Box 42)
  - Appalachian Regional Council for Health Assessment, Application for 2nd Year Conditional Designation, 1978-1979 (Box 42)
  - Hospital Corporation of America, Annual report, 1978 (Box 43)
  - Association of State and Territorial Health Officials, Annual report, 1978-1979 (Box 43)
  - Northwestern Virginia Health Systems Agency, Inc., 1980 Health Systems Plan for Virginia, Health Service Area I, 1978-1981 (Box 43)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Nutrition Task Force and Nutrition Program, 1978-1981 (Box 43)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Solid Waste and Vector Control, 1978-1981 (Box 43)
  - Eastern Virginia Health Systems Agency, Inc., Health Systems Plan, 1979 February (Box 43)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Emergency Medical Services, 1978-1981 (Box 43)
  - Summary and Analysis of Public Comments on Draft State Health Plan and Plan Development Committee Recommended REvisions to Draft Plan, 1979 (Box 44)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Engineering, 1978-1981 (Box 44)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Health Services Cost Review Act, 1978-1981 (Box 44)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Information Bulletins, 1975-1978 (Box 44)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Medicaid, Medical Assistance Program, 1978-1981 (Box 44)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Personnel (Review for privacy), 1978-1981 (Box 44)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Short and Long Range Plans, 1974-1976 (Box 44)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Swine Flu Immunization, 1976 (Box 44)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Toxic Substances Information Act, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Statewide Health Coordinating Council, 1978-1981 (Box 45)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Division of Water Programs, 1978-1981 (Box 45)
  - National Demonstration Water Project, A Sense of Urgency, 1978-1981 (Box 45)
  - General, Demonstration Water Project Inc., Roanoke, 1978-1981 (Box 45)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, General, 1978-1981 (Box 45)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Safe Water Drinking Act (P.L. 93-523), 1976-1978 (Box 45)
  - Kepone Facilities Plan, 1977 (Box 46)
  - Colonial Virginia Foundation for Medical Care, Grant Application, 1979 (Box 46)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Bureau of Sanitary Engineering, 1978-1981 (Box 46)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Statewide Health Coordinating Council, 1978-1981 (Box 46)
  - JLARC, Medical Assistance Programs in Virginia: An Overview, 1978 (Box 46)
  - JLARC, Long Term Care in Virginia, 1977 (Box 46)
  - Eastern Virginia Health Systems Agency, Inc., An Application for Full Designation of a Health Systems Agency for Eastern Virginia, 1978-1981 (Box 46)
  - Eastern Virginia Health Systems Agency Inc., Health Systems Plan, 2nd edition, 1979 (Box 47)
  - Appalachian Regional Council for Health Advancement Inc., ARCHA Health Systems Agency, Application for Full Designation as the Health Systems Agency for Tennessee Health Services Area I and Virginia Health Services Area VI, Volumes I and II, 1979-1980 (Box 47)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Task force on family planning, 1978-1981 (Box 47)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Health Regulatory Boards, General, 1978-1981 (Box 47)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, General, 1978-1981 (Box 47)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, General, 1978-1981 (Box 48)
  - Governor, Office of the, Governor's Toxic Substance Advisory Council, 1978-1981 (Box 48)
  - Making the National Health Planning Law Work: The State Perspective, National Governors Conference, 1977 (Box 48)
  - Report of the Tas Force on Medicaid Reform, National Governors Conference, 1977 (Box 48)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Health Planning and Resource Development Division, 1978-1981 (Box 48)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Legislation, 1978-1981 (Box 48)
  - Virginia State Health Plan, Volume I and II, 1978-1983 (Box 49)
  - Health Care Financing Administration Professional Standards Review, 1979 (Box 49)
  - Planning for Physician Requirements, A Manual to Develop Physician Requirement Models for HSAs, 1978 (Box 49)
  - Governor, Office of the, Overall Advisory Council on the Needs of Handicapped Children and Adults, 1978-1981 (Box 49)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, General, 1978-1981 (Box 49)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 10, Prevention Task Force, 1978-1981 (Box 50)
  - Governor, Office of the, National Governor's Association, 1978-1981 (Box 50)
  - General, Human Resources Liaison Committee, National Governor's Association, 1978-1981 (Box 50)
  - Office on Aging, Applicants, 1978-1981 (Box 50)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Word processing, 1978-1981 (Box 50)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Blood Assurance Program, 1978-1981 (Box 50)
  - General Assembly, Commission on Family Life (SJR 79), 1978 (Box 50)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Block grants, 1978-1981 (Box 51)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Refugee Resettlement, 1978-1981 (Box 51)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Virginia State Board of Medicine, Meeting, 1980 November 15-16 (Box 51)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Virginia State Board of Medicine, Meeting, 1981 March 29 (Box 51)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Virginia State Board of Medicine, Meeting, 1981 November 14-15 (Box 51)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Health Regulatory Boards, State Board of Medicine, General, 1981 (Box 51)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Project Enumeration, 1978-1981 (Box 51)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Energy Assistance Program, 1978-1981 (Box 51)
  - Dept. of Health Regulatory Boards, Virginia State Board of Medicine, 1980-1981 (Box 51)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 52)
  - Dept. of Intergovernmental Affairs, Urban Assistance Incentive Fund Advisory Committee, 1978 (Box 52)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget, Agency Guidance Memorandum, 1980-1982 (Box 52)
  - General Assembly, JLARC, 1978-1981 (Box 52)
  - General Assembly, Local Option SB 160, 1978 (Box 52)
  - Governor, Governor's Local Government Advisory Council, Executive Order 48, 1978-1981 (Box 52)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Energy Assistance Program, 1978-1981 (Box 52)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Refugee Resettlement, 1978-1981 (Box 52)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Refugees, 1978-1981 (Box 53)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Division of Social Services, 1978-1981 (Box 53)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Title XX Social Security Act, 1978-1981 (Box 53)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Refugee resettlement, 1978-1981 (Box 53)
  - Plan Manual for 1979-1980 Title XX Planning, 1978-1981 (Box 53)
  - Dept. of Welfare, Central Resource Listing: Residential Services provided by Agencies and Institutions to Children in Virginia, 1978-1981 (Box 53)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia, Comprehensive Annual Plan for Social Services under Title XX of the National Social Security Act, 1980-1981 (Box 53)
  - An Examination of Virginia Allocation of Federal Social Services Title XX Funds to Localities, Robert G. Kassebaum, 1979-1980 (Box 53)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, General, 1978-1981 (Box 54)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Division of Field Operations, 1978-1981 (Box 54)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Bureau of Fiscal Management, 1978-1981 (Box 54)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Division of Financial Services, 1978-1981 (Box 54)
  - General Assembly, Commissions and Committees, VALC Public Welfare System, 1978-1981 (Box 54)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Information and Referral System, 1978-1981 (Box 55)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Division of Licensing, 1978-1981 (Box 55)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Purchase of Service Program, 1978-1981 (Box 55)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, SSI, Optional Grant Program, 1978-1981 (Box 55)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Division of Social Services, 1978-1981 (Box 55)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Support Enforcement Program, 1978-1981 (Box 55)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Title XX, Social Security Act, 1978-1981 (Box 55)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, WERCS System, 1978-1981 (Box 55)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Work rule, 1978-1981 (Box 55)
  - National Welfare Reform: A Program for Change, National Governors Conference, Staff Task Force Report, 1977 (Box 55)
  - Task Force on Social Services, Report to the Honorable Otis L. Brown, Secretary of Human Affairs, Office of the Governor, On Social Services provided by Human Affairs Agencies in Virginia, 1975 (Box 55)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, General, 1978-1981 (Box 56)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Health Survey, 1978-1981 (Box 56)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Administration, 1978-1981 (Box 56)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Lynchburg Training School and Hospital, 1978-1981 (Box 56)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Deinstitutionalization Project, Northern Virginia Training Center, 1978-1981 (Box 56)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Western State Hospital, 1978-1981 (Box 57)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Planning and Budget, Biennial Budgets, 1978-1981 (Box 57)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Planning and Budget, General, 1978-1981 (Box 57)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Personnel and Training, General, 1978-1981 (Box 57)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Planning and Budget, Biennium, 1978-1980 (Box 58)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of General Services, Division of Engineering and Building, 1978-1981 (Box 58)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Purchases and Supply, 1978-1981 (Box 58)
  - The PRoceedings of the Assembly on the Dimensions of Hunger and Malnutrition, 1976 (Box 58)
  - VDOT, Transportation Services for Human Resources, 1979 Aug. (Box 58)
  - Va. Dept. of Welfare, Commonwealth of Va., Comprehensive Annual Plan for Social Services Under Title XX of the National Social Security Act, 1981-1982 (Box 58)
  - Children, Youth, and Families in Virginia: Assessing their needs, 1978 (Box 58)
  - Va. Center for Aging, Final Report of the Statewide Survey of Older Virginias, Vol. I, Methods and Procedures, 1978-1981 (Box 58)
  - Va. Center for Aging, Final Report of the Statewide Survey of Older Virginias, Vol. II, Findings, 1978-1981 (Box 58)
  - Proposed Virginia WIC Program, Plan of Program Operations and Administration, 1982 (Box 59)
  - Food Bibliography, 1977-1980 (Box 59)
  - Food in the Future, Proceedings of a Planning Symposium, 1981 (Box 59)
  - Statewide Conference on the Eating System: Making Virginia Policy on Food and Nutrition Proceedings, 1979 Nov. 27-28 (Box 59)
  - Food: Right or Privilege, Papers from a Conference on Ethics and Nutrition, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Proceedings of the Assembly on the Dimensions of Hunger and Nutrition, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - USDA, Day Care, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Virginia Association of Community Action Agencies, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Virginia Coalition for Cooperatives, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Final Report Subcommittee on Nutrition of the Virginia Council on Health and Medical Care of the Central Virginia HSA, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - USDA, Security block, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Virginia Cooperative Extension Services, Program, 1982 (Box 59)
  - Virginia State Health Plan, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - World Food Day, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Task Force on Food and Nutrition Policy, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Report of Interdept. Council on Food and Nutrition, 1982 (Box 59)
  - Dairy and Food Council of the Southeast Inc., Virginia Division, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Delmarva Rural Ministries, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, Brochures, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Dept. of Education, Health and Physical Education, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Dept. of Education, Nutrition Education and Training Program (NET), 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Dept. of Education, School food service, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Dept. of Health, Bureau of Nutrition Services, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Dept. of Health, WIC, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Dept. of Welfare, Food Stamp Program, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Dept. of Welfare, Division of Licensing, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Dept. of Welfare, Information and Referral Providers, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - American Cancer Society, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - American Diabetes Association, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Assembly Against Hunger and Malnutrition, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Assessments, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Bread for the World, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Center for Science in the Public Interest, Nutrition action, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Citizens Regional Conference on Hunger, Food, and Nutrition, 1979 (Box 59)
  - Community Nutrition Institute, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Conference on Alternative State and Local Policies, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Council on Food Nutrition, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Nutritional monitoring, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Nutrition survelliance, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
  - Other states Nutrition Council, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Food banks, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Food Law Project and mailing list, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Cooking suggestions, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Food provision background, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - HJR 306, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Infant mortality, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - La Leche League, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - March of Dimes, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Office on Aging, Nutrition Program, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Organized approach to risk reduction, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Organizational chart of Virginia, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Overview of nutrition programs in Virginia, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Public food and nutrition programs, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - "Raisin Up," 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Second Harvest, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - HR Planning retreat, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Secretary of Human Resources, General, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Memoranda (Agencies), 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - General, Southern Institute for Human Resources, Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 61)
  - Dept. of Welfare, 1976 (Box 62)
  - COVIS Planning Newsletters, 1978-1981 (Box 62)
  - Memorandum, 1978-1981 (Box 62)
  - MASD, 1975-1976 (Box 62)
  - MASD, ADP Information, 1978-1981 (Box 62)
  - JLARC, 1978-1981 (Box 62)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, General, 1978-1981 (Box 63)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Health Plan and Resource Development, 1978-1981 (Box 63)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Statewide Health Coordinating Council, 1978-1981 (Box 63)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Certificate of Need Program, 1978-1981 (Box 64)
  - Governor, Office of, Radioactive Waste Management Advisory Commission, 1978-1981 (Box 64)
  - An Application for Renewal of Full Designation of a Health Systems Agency for Eastern Virginia, 1978-1981 (Box 64)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Emergency Medical Services, 1978-1981 (Box 64)
  - Transfer of Blue Ridge Sanatorium to UVA, 1977 (Box 64)
  - Health Care Financing Grants and Contracts Report, 1978-1981 (Box 64)
  - Center for Health Statistics, Virginia 1978 Statistical Annual Report, 1978-1981 (Box 64)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Evaluation of Health Care for SW Va. Mental Health Institute, Catawba Hospital, and SW State Hospital, 1978-1981 (Box 64)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Virginia Substance Abuse Plan, 1980-1981 (Box 64)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Development Disabilities Planning Council, General, 1978-1981 (Box 65)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Commission for the Visually Handicapped, General, 1978-1981 (Box 65)
  - Governor, Office of, Governors Committee on the Education of the Handicapped, 1978-1981 (Box 65)
  - Report of the MRED (Mentally retarded emotionally disturbed) Project, 1980 (Box 65)
  - Other State Agencies, Intergovernmental Affairs, State/Federal Regulations, Legislative tracking, 1978-1981 (Box 66)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Intergovernmental Affairs, General, 1978-1981 (Box 66)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Intergovernmental Affairs, Office of Special Programs, 1978-1981 (Box 66)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Intergovernmental Affairs, A-95 Clearinghouse, 1978-1981 (Box 66)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Intergovernmental Affairs, Local and Regional Planning (Districts), 1978-1981 (Box 66)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Intergovernmental Affairs, Urban Assistance Incentive Fund Project, Resumes, 1978-1981 (Box 66)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Administration, 1978-1981 (Box 66)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (Prescription Team), Placement of Children, 1978-1981 (Box 66)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Data Services Division, 1978-1981 (Box 67)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Eastern State Hospital, 1978-1981 (Box 67)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Central State Hospital, 1978-1981 (Box 67)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Mental Retardation, 1978-1981 (Box 67)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Legislation, 1978-1981 (Box 67)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Mental Health, 1978-1981 (Box 67)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Information Director, 1978-1981 (Box 67)
  - JLARC, Program Evaluation, Virginia Drug Abuse Control Programs, 1975 (Box 67)
  - Plan for the Development of a Statewide Program for the Prevention of Mental Illness, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse in Virginia, 1978-1981 (Box 67)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Annual report, 1979-1980 (Box 67)
  - Subject files, A-102 Project ACIR, 1978-1981 (Box 68)